Our stock of the day in high value added is
Life Insurance Corporation i.e. LIC.
ICC Quality Research team has
given buy rating to LIC with the
target price of Rs. 975. 57.2%
aside. Just talk in next 12 months.
Now what is the rest for the stock? Let us know.
LIC has reported 15% YoY and same
up growth in Q3 2023 moderating it from
25% YoY in Q2 2023 and on
sequential basis marching down to
14.6% and Q3 from 15.2% in Q2 2023.
Direct company is interested to increase the
share of non-participating savings in non-
participating policies. The profits are not
shared and no difference is available to the
policy holders. This type of policy is also considered
non-participating without profit and non-
participating policy. Now what are the positive points?
First cost ratio has improved to 177.
This points driven  By lower commission and
higher business volume, second company profit
after tax registered what is 6300 crore
in Q3 f522 Now here we see a negative point
VNP March in for three
marks FII 23 was 14.6% lower than 15.2%
from K to FII 23
Today's our value history which you
can invest by taking part of one year To
know more such fundamentals,
you can go to our White Tea playlist
where a playlist is made in the name of Value Adjust
But before that
subscribe to our Contact
Security YouTube channel and hit the
bell icon Now you can also follow us on social media platforms
select Instagram Telegram Twitter
here
Documents Carefully Before Investing